

# chris McGLYNN

www.coderfoundry.com/chrismcglynn

# FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript JQuery

Bootstrap .NET

> C# MVC

ASP.NET

SOL

LINQ Xamarin

WebAPI

# CODER

1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer**

Kernersville, NC · July 2017–November 2017

- Created a personal portfolio and blog website using C#, MVC5 and JavaScript.
- Created a fully functional MVC bug tracker web application, from scratch, implementing enhanced security and file uploading features.
- Created a fully functional financial portal web application using .NET MVC framework. Composed dynamic front-end design using partial views and AJAX.
- Created a fully functioning mobile vehicle information application using Xamarin.
  Accessed NHTSA's car recalls database using WebAPI2. Included images using Bing's Cognitive Image Search API. Built RESTful APIs and utilized Azure App Services.

#### The Arrival Magazine, Music Editor

Winston Salem, NC · 2014-Current

- Responsible for writing, editing and publishing music genre articles.
- Conducts in-person audio and video interviews with local artists, businesses and restaurants that support the city of Winston Salem.
- Worked on several graphic design projects including CD layout, t shirt, promotional materials and logo design.

### **QPC Recording Studios, Owner/Operator**

Oak Ridge, NC · 2000–Current

- Tracking, mixing and mastering audio for over fifteen years.
- Played and recorded guitar/bass for multiple local musical acts.
- Highly proficient with the leading industry standard recording software, Pro Tools.

## **EDUCATION**

Guilford Technical Community College, Recording/Audio Engineering Jamestown, NC · 2001